pkgames.net 2014-06-27

# Free Download Full Version: Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

www.pkgames.net respects the privacy of all users and shall ensure that the personal information you may provide is treated confidentially.

haroon.gul9@gmail.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.pkgames.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. haroon.gul9@gmail.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.pkgames.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Internet Explorer  
Firefox  
Safari  
Chrome  
Opera  
If you have suggestions, Questions or complains about our Privacy Policy? please send a mail to haroon.gul9@gmail.com
